Guide to the Nancy Mason Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
Nancy Mason papers
circa 1941-2014
University of Washington Libraries Special Collections Box 352900 Seattle, WA 98195-2900
6055
6055-001
Mason, Nancy
8.29 cubic feet 10 boxes including 12 VHS tapes, and 1 oversize folder
Materials related to Nancy Mason's work as a longtime tradeswoman activist
Nancy Mason began her working life as an English and history teacher at Franklin High School in Seattle. In 1979, she made a career change by entering the four-year inside wireman electrical apprenticeship program. In addition to working as a journeyman electrician, Nancy has also served as the Training Director at the Puget Sound Electrical Apprenticeship, as the Apprenticeship Program Manager for the Washington State Department of Labor and Industries, as a labor trustee at the Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship Training Committee and as a business representative at IBEW, Local 46. Mason has also been a longtime tradeswoman activist throughout her career, advocating for the importance of apprenticeship for people of color and women to get into the trades and on the importance of apprenticeship as a highly skilled career path; "the other four year degree".
Programs, memorandums, studies, reports,correspondence, materials from the Washington State Department of Labor and Industries, Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee, and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW).
Forms part of the Labor Archives of Washington.
Closed until processed
Mason, Nancy$c(Labor union member)$vArchives; Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Labor$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor movement$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Labor unions$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Women labor union members$zWashington (State)$zSeattle; Personal correspondence; Records (Documents)
Labor Archives of Washington (University of Washington); Personal Papers/Corporate Records; Women; Labor Unions; Labor History
- Booklet on Studies in Industry and Employment: Apprenticeship, September 1998 (Box-folder 1/1)
- NOW Legal Defense and Education Fund Meeting: Report, Correspondence and Short Biographies, November 5, 2001 - November 29, 2001 (Box-folder 1/2)
- Washington Apprenticeship Workshop and Presentation Printouts, July 28, 2001 - October 10, 2001 (Box-folder 1/3)
- Nancy Mason's Resignation Correspondence, May 8, 2006 - May 24, 2006 (Box-folder 1/4)
- Washington State Apprenticeship and Training Council Quarterly Meeting: Wage Laws, January 18, 2001 (Box-folder 1/5)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Guides, 1990 - 2005 (Box-folder 1/6)
- AFL-CIO Mobilization Guide, 1997 (Box-folder 1/7)
- Washington Department of Labor and Industries: Prevailing Wage Laws Booklet, May 2005 (Box-folder 1/8)
- Apprenticeship Coordinators and Debrief Meetings, April 16, 2001 - October 30, 2001 (Box-folder 1/9)
- Apprenticeship Reciprocal Agreement: Washington, Oregon, and Idaho, June 11, 1997 - September 29, 1997 (Box-folder 1/10)
- Apprenticeship RCWs, WACs, and Presentation Printouts, July 22, 2001 - November 1, 2001 (Box-folder 1/11)
- Review on Washington's Apprenticeship Policies, March 22, 1999 - September 8, 1999 (Box-folder 1/12)
- Apprenticeship Projections and Correspondence between Directors, October 2, 2001 - October 17, 2001 (Box-folder 1/13)
- Sample Labor and Industries Claims Forms, March 19, 1997 (Box-folder 1/14)
- Governor's Industrial Safety and Health Conference, September 26, 2001 - September 27, 2001 (Box-folder 1/15)
- Manager Development and Performance Plan, November 2004 - March 10, 2005 (Box-folder 1/16)
- Guidelines on Media Presence, Undated (Box-folder 1/17)
- Apprenticeship Program Manager Position Description, December 2, 1997 (Box-folder 1/18)
- Labor and Industries Email Correspondence, April 12, 2005 - September 16, 2005 (Box-folder 1/19)
- Letter from Congressman Adam Smith, September 14, 2005 - September 15, 2005 (Box-folder 1/20)
- Nancy Mason's Calendar of Events, January 2009 - December 2009 (Box-folder 1/21)
- Labor and Industries Award, 2001 (Box-folder 1/22)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Diversity Training, October 22, 2009 - 2012 (Box-folder 1/23)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Training and Retirement Certificates, September 6, 1997 - January 2014 (Box-folder 1/24)
- Bureau of Fire Investigation Interview Sheets from Susan Eisenberg, January 16, 2010 - February 18, 2010 (Box-folder 1/25)
- Cover Letter and Job Description for Wider Opportunities for Women, March 19, 2010 (Box-folder 1/26)
- Susan Eisenberg's Interview with Nancy Mason, October 1992 (Box-folder 1/27)
- American Society for Training and Development Toolkit, September 1992 (Box-folder 1/28)
- TRAINING Magazine's Compilation Book on Adult Learning, 1989 (Box-folder 1/29)
- Electrical Apprenticeship Graduation Banquet Programs, November 12, 1983 - October 29, 1994 (Box-folder 1/30)
- Letter of Appreciation from Lloyd Hara, July 2009 (Box-folder 1/31)
- Photos of International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Workers Picketing, Undated (Box-folder 1/32)
- Steve Washburn's Letter of Recommendation for Nancy Mason as Apprenticeship Program Manager, January 22, 1996 - June 12, 1997 (Box-folder 1/33)
- Financial Guide for Apprenticeship Programs, 2006 (Box-folder 1/34)
- International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans Conference Certificates, October 7, 2006 - October 11, 2006 (Box-folder 1/35)
- World of Work Inventory Career Profile Report, November 14, 2009 (Box-folder 1/36)
- Vanna Novak's Guide for Women in Business, 2006 (Box-folder 1/37)
- Girl Scout Leader Magazine, April 1994 (Box-folder 1/38)
- Oregon Tradeswomen Leadership Institute, March 30, 2007 - June 13, 2007 (Box-folder 1/39)
- Health Support Specialist Registered Apprenticeship Program Handbook, February 17, 2005 - June 21, 2005 (Box-folder 1/40)
- Washington's Strategic Plan for Workforce Development, 2006 - January 2007 (Box-folder 1/41)
- National Association of Workforce Development Professionals (NAWDP) Certified Workforce Development Professional Application Package, February 9, 2006 - January 31, 2007 (Box-folder 1/42)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) 75th Anniversary Banquet Program and History Booklet, October 14, 1989 (Box-folder 1/43)
- Frank Oleson's Evaluation of Nancy Mason for Apprenticeship Director Selection, May 19, 1989 (Box-folder 1/44)
- National Alliance of State and Territorial Aids Directors (NASTAD) 55th Annual Apprenticeship Conference, August 10, 2005 - August 11, 2005 (Box-folder 1/45)
- Cascade Center for Public Service: Executive Refresher Program Binder, October 14, 2003 - October 31, 2003 (Box-folder 1/46)
- Cascade Center for Public Service: Management Series Class on Communication, April 5, 2004 - May 7, 2004 (Box-folder 1/47)
- Strategic Leadership Training Binder (1 of 2), May 10, 2001 - June 7, 2001 (Box-folder 1/48)
- Strategic Leadership Training Binder (2 of 2), May 10, 2001 - June 7, 2001 (Box-folder 1/49)
- Puget Sound Solar Project, January 29, 2008 (Box-folder 1/50)
- Time and Activity Logs for LM-2 Annual Reports, January 2006 - December 2008 (Box-folder 1/51)
- Sound Transit Diversity Oversight Committee, April 29, 2004 - April 18, 2008 (Box-folder 1/52)
- IBEW Letter on Wages and Benefits, November 29, 2007 (Box-folder 1/53)
- IBEW Apprentice Meeting Notes, October 11, 2007 - January 10, 2008 (Box-folder 2/1)
- Letter of Appointment to the Safety and Health Investment Projects Program Advisory Committee from Labor and Industries, January 11, 2008 (Box-folder 2/2)
- Apollo Alliance of Washington: Alternative Energy, June 2004 - July 6, 2006 (Box-folder 2/3)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Internal Policies and Sexual Harassment Printouts, April 28, 2003 - May 14, 2003 (Box-folder 2/4)
- Letter from International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) to Senator Prentice, C. 2005 (Box-folder 2/5)
- Apprenticeship Utilization Goals and Requirements Study, 2005 - December 2007 (Box-folder 2/6)
- Registered Apprenticeship Programs Study Report by the U.S. Government Accountability Office, August 2005 (Box-folder 2/7)
- Helmets to Hardhats: Washington Building and Construction Trades Initiative, 2008 (Box-folder 2/8)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Hours Worked, 1996 - December 13, 2007 (Box-folder 2/9)
- Labor and Industries 2006 Compliance Review and Program Application, December 8, 2007 (Box-folder 2/10)
- Labor and Industries Prevailing Wage Laws, February 11, 1985 (Box-folder 2/11)
- Federal Committee on Apprenticeship: Policy Recommendation, January 8, 1992 (Box-folder 2/12)
- Washington State Building and Construction Trades Council Apprenticeship Program Report, February 15, 2005 (Box-folder 2/13)
- Washington State Tax Rate Information for Employers, January 3, 2008 (Box-folder 2/14)
- Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee (PSEJATC) Standards, May 23, 1941 - July 21, 2006 (Box-folder 2/15-2/16)
- Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee (PSEJATC) Minutes, August 8, 2006 - June 12, 2007 (Box-folder 2/17)
- Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee (PSEJATC) Correspondence, March 22, 2005 - July 10, 2006 (Box-folder 2/18)
- Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee (PSEJATC) Expense Log for Reimbursement, October 6, 2006 - October 11, 2006 (Box-folder 2/19)
- Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee (PSEJATC) Trust Fund Agreement, October 24, 2000 - November 6, 2000 (Box-folder 2/20)
- Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee (PSEJATC) Outreach Materials, April 24, 2004 - 2006 (Box-folder 2/21)
- Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee (PSEJATC) Miscellaneous, March 3, 2003 - August 30, 2006 (Box-folder 2/22)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Grievance Summary and Forms, October 1992 - June 11, 2003 (Box-folder 2/23)
- Article on Retrospective Rating program, March 8, 2005 (Box-folder 2/24)
- General Article on Unions, July 14, 2005 (Box-folder 2/25)
- Union Politics: Articles and Cartoons, 1988 - 2003 (Box-folder 2/26)
- Institute for Environmental Research and Education: Articles and Information, July 27, 2005 - August 3, 2005 (Box-folder 2/27)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Labor Relations Letter on Partnering, April 15, 2003 - April 28, 2003 (Box-folder 2/28)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Internal Policies and Correnspondence, 2003 - May 8, 2008 (Box-folder 2/29)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Union Officer Elections, 2005 - 2008 (Box-folder 2/30)
- Miscellaneous Maps, November 8, 2004 - May 27, 2005 (Box-folder 2/31)
- Industrial Areas Foundation: Broad-Based Organizing, April 26, 2005 (Box-folder 2/32)
- Job Site Visits and Information Sheets, July 7, 2006 - July 31, 2006 (Box-folder 2/33)
- Nany Mason's International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Expense Reports, October 11, 2006 - December 11, 2009 (Box-folder 2/34)
- HVAC/R Task Force Electrical Hours Verification Proposal, July 3, 2006 - August 10, 2006 (Box-folder 2/35)
- HVAC/R Task Force Licensing Requirements, September 14, 2005 - December 2005 (Box-folder 2/36)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Journal Article by Bill Moyers, 2003 (Box-folder 2/37)
- Articles on Union Busting, December 14, 2004 (Box-folder 2/38)
- AFL-CIO Voice At Work Campaign, October 13, 2003 - December 10, 2003 (Box-folder 2/39)
- Anti-Union Letter from U.S. Senator David Vitter to IBEW Member, September 16, 2005 (Box-folder 2/40)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Agenda, April 28, 2007 (Box-folder 2/41)
- Parliamentary Procedure Training for Effective Union Meetings, April 7, 2007 - February 26, 2011 (Box-folder 2/42)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Constitution and Bylaws 2006-2009, September 2006 - September 14, 2009 (Box-folder 2/43)
- Leadership Communication Skills Worksheet Packet, January 26, 2008 (Box-folder 2/44)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Legislative/Political Primer, September 9, 2006 (Box-folder 2/45)
- National Labor College Course Catalog, 2007 - 2008 (Box-folder 2/46)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Leadership and Ethics, April 12, 2008 (Box-folder 2/47)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Advanced Organizing, March 1, 2008 (Box-folder 2/48)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Operations of the Local, March 15, 2008 (Box-folder 2/49)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Building More Inclusive Unions 2008, September 13, 2008 (Box-folder 2/50)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Introduction to Labor History 2008, September 27, 2008 (Box-folder 2/51)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Introduction to Organizing, November 8, 2008 (Box-folder 2/52)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Representation Skills, November 22, 2008 (Box-folder 2/53)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Trust Funds and Trustee Duties, December 13, 2008 (Box-folder 2/54-2/55)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder: Building More Inclusive Unions 2009, October 10, 2009 (Box-folder 2/56)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training Binder:Introduction to Labor History 2009, October 24, 2009 (Box-folder 3/1)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Leadership Training CD-Rom, Undated (Box-folder 3/2)
- Holmes Electric Company Policy and Procedure Manual, January 1987 (Box-folder 3/3)
- Foreman's Training: Articles on Race and Sexual Harassment, January 24, 1992 - August 4, 1992 (Box-folder 3/4)
- Intensive Training Program Binder, January 13, 1992 - January 17, 1992 (Box-folder 3/5)
- Sex and Power Issues Conference, March 20, 1992 - March 21, 1992 (Box-folder 3/6-3/7)
- National Training Institute Commencement and Awards/Recognition Banquet Program, August 11, 1995 (Box-folder 3/8)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Constitution 1978, October 1978 (Box-folder 3/9)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Constitution and Agreement 1980-1983, June 1, 1980 - May 31, 1983 (Box-folder 3/10)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Constitution and Agreement 1986-1988, June 30, 1986 - May 31, 1988 (Box-folder 3/11)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Constitution and Agreements 1988-1996, July 11, 1988 - May 31, 1996 (Box-folder 3/12)
- Gould Shawmut Book of Electrical Information, 1983 (Box-folder 3/13)
- Survey and Manual on Gender Stereotyping for School Personnel, 1979 (Box-folder 3/14)
- Shortchanging Girls: Survey Results and Articles on Attitudes between Genders, January 1991 (Box-folder 3/15)
- Diversity at Work: Conference Packet and Articles, April 9, 1990 - February 28, 1992 (Box-folder 3/16)
- Northwest Women's Law Center: Publications on Sexual Harassment, 1988 - 1992 (Box-folder 3/17)
- Letter on Nancy Mason's Sexual Harassment Class, March 25, 1992 (Box-folder 3/18)
- Publications on Affirmative Action, 1992 - August 16, 1995 (Box-folder 3/19)
- Tradeswomen Articles by Susan Eisenberg, September 1990 - June 1991 (Box-folder 3/20)
- Letter to Nancy Mason from Susan Eisenberg, August 21, 1992 (Box-folder 3/21)
- Interview Article with Betty Friedan, August 1993 (Box-folder 3/22)
- Sexual Harassment Complaints: Issues and Implications for Union Representatives, Undated (Box-folder 3/23)
- Washington State Sexual Harassment Policy and Intervention Manual, January 9, 1984 (Box-folder 3/24)
- Union Women and Labor Law at The Evergreen State College, April 25, 1989 - June 18, 1989 (Box-folder 3/25)
- National Electrical Contractors Association (NECA) Reports on Preventing Sexual Harassment in the Electrical Construction Industry, October 24, 1990 - March 25, 1995 (Box-folder 3/26)
- Title VII Guidelines and Brochures, January 19, 1979 - February 6, 1991 (Box-folder 3/27-3/28)
- People Magazine: Sex and the Boss, October 28, 1991 (Box-folder 3/29)
- Job Training Opportunities for Women in Construction, March 19, 1989 (Box-folder 3/30)
- Apprenticeship Training: Prevention of Harassment, December 9, 1991 (Box-folder 3/31)
- Nancy Mason's Presentation Notes: Women Apprentices and Harassment, 1991 (Box-folder 3/32)
- Title IX Binder, December 1978 - April 23, 1979 (Box-folder 3/33)
- Employment Law Briefings: Sexual Harassment in the Workplace, March 29, 1989 - March 30, 1989 (Box-folder 3/34)
- Labor Center Diversity Education Program, 1988 - January 24, 1994 (Box-folder 3/35)
- Horace Mann League: Education and Religion, Undated (Box-folder 3/36)
- Articles and Brochures on Diversity, July 1989 - March 4, 1992 (Box-folder 3/37)
- Letter and Newsletter on Racism from North Seattle Community College, January 24, 1991 - November 25, 1991 (Box-folder 3/38)
- Equity Institute Membership Letter and Newsletter, May 1991 - December 5, 1991 (Box-folder 3/39)
- Letters from Mary Sebek, March 12, 1990 - July 24, 1991 (Box-folder 3/40)
- Women in the Workplace, March 1990 - April 1995 (Box-folder 3/41)
- Letter on Harris v. Forklift Systems, Inc., November 15, 1993 (Box-folder 3/42)
- Interview with Feminists in Non-Traditional Trades, December 3, 1990 (Box-folder 3/43)
- Sexual Harassment Prevention Manual for Management Personnel, 1988 (Box-folder 3/44)
- Washington State Human Rights News Review, January 4, 1993 - January 11, 1995 (Box-folder 3/45)
- Publications on Handling Sexual Harassment and Discrimination, November 1992 (Box-folder 3/46)
- Seattle Community Colleges Letter on Title VII and Sexual Harassment, October 18, 1991 (Box-folder 3/47)
- Letters on Sexual Discrimination with Copy of Robinson v. Jacksonville Shipyards, Inc., July 12, 1991 - October 21, 1991 (Box-folder 3/48)
- City of Seattle Office for Women's Rights: Guide for Male Supervisors in Labor Occupations, November 10, 1982 (Box-folder 3/49)
- National Organization for Women Newsletters, September 5, 1985 - October 8, 1985 (Box-folder 3/50)
- Union Framework Article by Susan Eisenberg, December 1991 (Box-folder 3/51)
- Short Biography on Molly Martin, November 1988 (Box-folder 3/52)
- Letter from Judith Kurtz on Women in Trades Fair, December 7, 1990 (Box-folder 3/53)
- Gender Discrimination at Seattle City Light, February 16, 1983 - February 21, 1983 (Box-folder 4/1)
- Affirmative Action Newspaper Articles, November 1990 - February 1992 (Box-folder 4/2)
- Article on Cost of Living, October 18, 1992 (Box-folder 4/3)
- National Apprenticeship Training Binder, August 11, 2009 (Box-folder 4/4-4/5)
- Copy of the Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, April 22, 2003 (Box-folder 4/6)
- National Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee (NJATC) Handbook, 1999 (Box-folder 4/7)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Constitution and Labor Agreement, September 2001 - May 31, 2007 (Box-folder 4/8)
- Women of Achievement Awards Press Release, March 17, 1995 (Box-folder 4/9)
- Article on the North American Free Trade Agreement (NAFTA), November 18, 1993 (Box-folder 4/10)
- Commemorative Copy of the 1891 Report of the Proceedings of the First Annual Convention of the National Brotherhood of Electrical Workers of America, 1991 (Box-folder 4/11)
- Oversize Newspaper Articles, March 1989 - August 2000 (Box-folder 5/1)
- Posters, Undated (Box-folder 5/2-5/3)
- Hat and Books bill, photo and letter, 2004 (Box-folder 5/4)
- National Alliance of State and Territorial Aids Directors (NASTAD) Appreciation Plaque with Clock, 2006 (Box-folder 6/1)
- Washington State Apprenticeship and Training Council Appreciation Plaque, Undated (Box-folder 6/2)
- Nancy Mason's Training Director Award Plaque, 1996 (Box-folder 6/3)
- Washington State Apprenticeship and Training Council Certificate of Meritorius Service, May 23, 2006 (Box-folder 6/4)
- Puget Sound Electrical Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee (PSEJATC) Excellence Plaque, 1996 (Box-folder 6/5)
- Central Contractors Association, Inc Excellence in Service Plaque, July 1991 (Box-folder 6/6)
- Union T-Shirts and Jacket, C. 1990 - 1995 (Box-folder 7/1)
- Recognition of Dedicated Service from the Washington State Department of Labor and Industries to Nancy Mason, January 26, 2005 (Box-folder 7/2)
- Mug 1998 Northwest States Electrical Contest NECA/IBEW (Box-folder 7/3)
- Department of Labor and Industries Speciality Compliance Services Community Service Ribbon, 2004 (Box-folder 8/1)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) New Business Manager Training PowerPoint Presentations, June 2007 (Box-folder 8/2)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) New Business Manager Training References I, II and III (Construction), July 2007 - September 2007 (Box-folder 8/3)
- Writing Tips from the International Labor Communications Association, Undated (Box-folder 8/4)
- Department of Public Safety: Public Disclosure Index of Records, April 15, 1986 - November 7, 2006 (Box-folder 8/5)
- Assault On Workers' Rights Case Studies, 1994 (Box-folder 8/6)
- International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW) Bargaining Units Under the Deklewa Decision, August 1987 - April 1988 (Box-folder 8/7)
- Teaching Techniques for Labor Education Handbook, 2002 (Box-folder 8/8)
- Working Smart: A Union Guide to Participation Programs and Reengineering Labor Notes Book, 1994 (Box-folder 8/9)
- Shop Steward Training Conference Binder, September 23, 2008 - September 25, 2008 (Box-folder 8/10-8/11)
- Book of Poems by Susan Eisenberg, 1984 (Box-folder 8/12)
- Monthly Personal Service Contracts, Goods and Services, and Travel Reports, September 2001 (Box-folder 8/13)
- Apprenticeship Meeting Notes, November 1, 2001 (Box-folder 8/14)
- Fire Service Joint Labor Management Candidate Ability Test, April 1, 1999 (Box-folder 8/15)
- Northwest Apprenticeship Reciprocal Agreement, August 2001 (Box-folder 8/16)
- Apprenticeship and Nontraditional Employment for Women (ANEW) Board Meeting, September 26, 2001 (Box-folder 8/17)
- Newsletter from Tradeswomen Now and Tomorrow, September 10, 2001 (Box-folder 8/18)
- Preapprenticeship Summit Meeting Report, April 17, 2001 (Box-folder 8/19)
- Washington State's Workforce Training Results, 1998 - 2000 (Box-folder 8/20)
- Washington State Employment Security Study on Apprenticeship, September 1998 (Box-folder 8/21)
- U.S. General Accounting Office Report on Registered Apprenticeships, September 2001 (Box-folder 8/22)
- Workforce Leadership Conference Folder, October 10, 2001 - October 11, 2001 (Box-folder 8/23)
- Women in the Construction Zone Book and Postcard, 1989 - 1991 (Box-folder 8/24)
- United States Apprenticeship Association (USAA) Sentinel Newsletters, April 2001 - December 2001 (Box-folder 8/25)
- Additional Apprenticeship Program Funding Application, July 2001 - 2002 (Box-folder 8/26)
- Department of Labor and Industries Speciality Compliance Services Meeting Notes and News Clippings, July 2001 - September 2001 (Box-folder 8/27)
- South Puget Sound Joint Apprenticeship and Training Committee Advisory Meeting Notes, May 15, 2001 (Box-folder 8/28)
- New York City Commission on Human Rights: Testimony of IBEW, Local 3 President Thomas van Arsdale, April 26, 1990 (Box-folder 8/29)